<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>clicl.</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on clicl.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 13:50:33 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Now</title>
      <link>/notif/now/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 13:50:33 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/notif/now/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;m not commissioning any freelance work at the moment. I&#39;m too busy fulfilling my dream as a professional internet troll during my spare time. Also, moonlighting as a meme thief takes off some of my time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Me</title>
      <link>/about/me/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 10:01:27 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/me/</guid>
      <description>Hi! I&#39;m clickfanatic. I go by the name Kristine in real life and normally I&#39;m not this blue. I&#39;m a former freelance web designer/PHP developer from the Philippines now focusing on the care of actual human beings a.k.a BS Nursing.
I coded this site using Bulma CSS, compiled with SASS, and then ported it to HUGO. I&#39;m currently leeching off Github Pages for hosting cause I&#39;m broke. All the tools I used to build this site are opensource.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hello hugo</title>
      <link>/ramblings/hello-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2019 17:59:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ramblings/hello-hugo/</guid>
      <description>After a few hours of tinkering with Jekyll for my blog, I&#39;ve finally made the jump to HUGO. Setup is easy and straightforward, It took me more time in deciding which theme to use and which host to deploy my site than the setup itself.
Installation Since I&#39;m on Arch Linux, installation is as easy as:
$ sudo pacman -S hugo Creating a site Now that HUGO is installed, create a new site by running</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>